<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Secondary Cities</title>
    <description>Resiliency - Human Security - Emergency Preparedness
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 01:38:07 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 01:38:07 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dynamic Mapping of Secondary Cities Symposium 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Secondary Cities in the developing world are rapidly growing urban areas that are regional hubs for commerce, services, and governance in developing countries that often do not have adequate planning mechanisms for future development and growth. This symposium will focus on the foremost data collection tools and technologies used to map urbanization in such cities. It is part of the Secondary Cities initiative, a global collaboration of universities and organizations supported by the Humanitarian Information Unit of the Office of the Geographer of the State Department.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/events/sample-event.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/events/sample-event.html</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        
        <category>events</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dynamic Mapping of Secondary Cities Symposium 2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Secondary Cities in the developing world are rapidly growing urban areas that are regional hubs for commerce, services, and governance in developing countries that often do not have adequate planning mechanisms for future development and growth. This symposium will focus on the foremost data collection tools and technologies used to map urbanization in such cities. It is part of the Secondary Cities initiative, a global collaboration of universities and organizations supported by the Humanitarian Information Unit of the Office of the Geographer of the State Department.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/events/sample-event-page-2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/events/sample-event-page-2.html</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        
        <category>events</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dynamic Mapping of Secondary Cities Symposium</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Secondary Cities in the developing world are rapidly growing urban areas that are regional hubs for commerce, services, and governance in developing countries that often do not have adequate planning mechanisms for future development and growth. This symposium will focus on the foremost data collection tools and technologies used to map urbanization in such cities. It is part of the Secondary Cities initiative, a global collaboration of universities and organizations supported by the Humanitarian Information Unit of the Office of the Geographer of the State Department.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/events/dynamic-mapping-symp.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/events/dynamic-mapping-symp.html</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        
        <category>events</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pokhara, Nepal</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Considered Nepal’s most picturesque destination, Pokhara is located in a tectonically active valley surrounded by the Himalayan and Mahabharat Mountain Ranges.  The Seti River and tributaries flow from these mountains and freshwater lakes are located throughout the city.  The same geological features that contribute to Pokhara’s natural beauty cause its volatility.  The United Nations Development Programme ranks Nepal 11th in the world for its susceptibility to natural disasters that include earthquakes, floods, landslides, drought, and sinkholes.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 15:08:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/pokhara.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/pokhara.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>cities</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mekelle, Ethiopia</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mekelle is the capital city of the Tigray Regional State of Ethiopia. It is one of the principal economic, cultural, political, and educational centers of the country. Mekelle is known for the cultural landmarks that include Ethiopian Orthodox churches and historic castles. Climate extremes are characteristic of the region. Mekelle is experiencing severe water problems that include lack of an adequate supply and quality issues.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 15:08:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/mekelle.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/mekelle.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>cities</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medellin, Colombia</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Medellin is the capital of the mountainous Antioquia province of Colombia.  The metropolitan area of Medellin includes nine other cities and is the second largest urban agglomeration in the country.  Medellin is a hub of economic, education and cultural activity and at the forefront of urban development for innovation, livability, and urban sustainability.  Rapid urban growth and migration have created challenges for future planning.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 15:08:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/medellin.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/medellin.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>cities</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kharkiv, Ukraine</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Kharkiv was founded in 1654 as a small fortress that grew to become a major center of Ukrainian culture within the Russian Empire.  The city functioned as the first capital of the Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic until 1935, after which the capital was relocated to Kiev. Kharkiv is the administrative center of Kharkiv Oblast and of the surrounding Kharkiv district.  The city’s population is the second largest in Ukraine.  Although the majority of the population is Ukrainian both in nationality and ethnicity, Kharkiv’s largest minority is of Russian descent due to its history and proximity to Russia.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 15:08:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/kharkiv.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/kharkiv.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>cities</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Denpasar, Indonesia</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Denpasar is the capital of Bali island and has the highest growth rate in Bali Province where tourism has expanded massively in recent years. The city is a hub for other cities in eastern Indonesia. Due to development pressures, Denpasar has experienced rapid physical, economic, and cultural change. Informal growth and the expanding tourist industry have fueled significant problems for waste management, particularly ocean trash.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 15:08:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/denpasar.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/denpasar.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>cities</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cusco,           Peru</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Cusco is located in the highlands of southeastern Peru at an elevation of 3,400 meters.  It is the capital of the Cusco region and province, and has an estimated population of more than 435,000.  From the 13th – 16th C, the city was capital of the Incan Empire, which led to its designation as a UNESCO World Heritage Site.  It serves as a gateway to the famous ruins of Machu Picchu, making it a renowned global tourist destination.  In recent decades, Cusco has experienced rapid urban growth and land use displacement, especially in the higher elevation districts of Santiago, San Sebastian and San Jeronimo.  These locations are particularly susceptible to earthquakes, landslides, and flooding.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 15:08:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/cusco.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/cities/cusco.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>cities</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect Camps</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Connect Camps offer an opportunity for alumni of the Mandela Washington Fellowship to share the professional skills and networks they acquired from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://youngafricanleaders.state.gov/washington-fellowship/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Young African Leaders Initiative&lt;/a&gt; with other young African leaders in their rural communities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/events/connect-camps.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/SecondaryCities2/events/connect-camps.html</guid>
        
        <category>event</category>
        
        
        <category>events</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
